♪ This is what we live for♪
♪ Woo-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Make it rain on the dance floor ♪
[Christine] Friday the 13th,
talk about that on camera.
[Heather] This stuff is so fun.
-Ooh, look at these.
-Oh, my God. That little backpack.
Right? That's what I was thinking.
Those are cute.
-Those are adorable.
-Oh, my God.
-That's so you I feel like.
-I love that.
-Hi.
-Oh, thank you.
[Heather] Thank you.
Here, I don't wanna make it fall.
There we go.
-[clerk 1] There we go.
-[Davina] Thank you.
[all] Cheers.
[chuckles] I like that.
-[Christine] The new Balmain jacket.
-I love that.
-It's a little big, but it's fun.
-[Davina] That's my fave.
I love it. This is very, like,
"I just killed my husband" vibes.
-Ooh, I love that.
-[Christine] I love that.
Let me throw on my fancy robe
after I just stabbed my man.
-[Christine] I think this is a winner.
-I love...
-[Heather] Look at her little evil look.
-[Davina] It's super creepy.
I haven't had a Red Bull,
I'm, like, dragging ass.
[Christine] I'm really into,
like, chains these days.
[Heather] Whips and chains?
I mean, always, that's everyday.
[girls laughing]
So, yeah, what's the
shopping occasion today?
Like, just retail therapy.
-[Heather] De-stressing?
-Guys, you have no idea.
-What?
-What's the deal?
I had a situation with Mary.
What? When?
[Christine] Mm-hmm. So, she came
to show a client my house.
-[Davina] Just like, "Really?"
-It was interesting to say the least.
She was really mad that I told you about
you not being invited to the wedding.
The only thing that she could say was
that I wasn't loyal.
And I was like, "Actually, the opposite.
I think someone doesn't talk to me,
to this day,
because I was so loyal towards
you and Romain."
She was just like,
"Well, no. That..." It was just...
-[Christine] She had nothing to say.
-Yeah.
No rebuttal.
So, did you and Mary end
on a bad note?
[mocking] She goes, "Well... Uh! Uh!
Chrishell was right about you. Oh!"
-What?
-And then she storms off.
-I know.
-Right about what?
I don't know. I mean, not being loyal.
After everything that's happened between
Mary and I, I just want to move on
and forget it all,
but there's definitely tension in the air.
So, send that dress,
the two Blazers, the pink one,
the wool one and the navy one to my house.
-[clerk 2] You got it.
-Thank you so much!
-All right, I'll see you soon. Bye, honey.
-[clerk 2] I'll see you soon.
-[Heather] Do you feel less stressed now?
-[Christine] About what?
♪ If you feel good let me hear you say ♪
♪ If you're feelin' good
Let me hear you say ♪
♪ If it feels good let me hear you say ♪
[Nicole] Wait,
so have you been here before?
[Mary] No, no.
[Nicole] So you have no idea
what we're gonna look at?
I have walked by Flora Vere so many times.
It's an absolutely magical,
like, hidden gem.
I'm just hoping that I find
my dream dress.
-[Chrishell] Oh, wow!
-[Mary] Right?
-Hi. Welcome.
-Thank you.
Mary. Nice to meet you.
I'm Sabrina. I'm going to be your stylist.
Perfect. I have one more person coming.
She's just running a few minutes behind.
No problem.
How about a little bit of bubbly?
-Oh. Yes.
-Yeah.
Let me pour some of the Grand Courtage.
You guys have a peek around.
-[cork pops]
-[Nicole] Woo.
[Chrishell] Yay!
It's happening. It's happening
-[Nicole] Let's get this party started.
-To finding the dress.
-[Mary] Cheers, ladies.
-Cheers.Yay!
[Sabrina] All right. One, two, three.
-[Mary] There she is.
-Hey.
-[Sabrina] Oh, a little bubbly for you?
-Yes, please.
I'll just take the bottle if you just...
-Yes, right?
-Yeah, I'm hardcore. [chuckles]
Between full-time single Mom of two,
real estate agent, home stager,
Maid of Honor duties,
I like...
[stuttering] There's not enough
of me to go around.
Something has to give.
[Amanza] Seriously, thank you.
[Sabrina] Overall for the wedding,
what are we hoping for?
-I want sophisticated, sexy, but simple.
-[Amanza] Oh, no.
[all laughing]
Aw, this is like a girl's dream.
I love this store.
[Amanza] This whole place is adorable.
[Mary] Ah!
[Sabrina]
It's a full French lace in the skirt.
[Mary] I really like this.
My wedding dress was spaghetti strap
and beaded and had lots of feathers,
a little high-low.
My style is definitely
a little more blingy.
I don't want it to be too sexy.
I have to find that perfect middle ground.
-Classy and trashy.
-Exactly.
-[girls chuckling]
-When I got married to my ex,
I got this dress that I envisioned.
it was a princess cut, full gown,
Monique Lhuillier,
like, very intricate design.
I think Mary is a little more chill,
a little more low-key.
-You have to try this on.
-That's pretty.
It's a little conservative though, right?
-Just humor me, just try it on.
-Okay.
[Sabrina] We're going to get started.
You ladies can all have a seat.
Okay.
And you're going to follow me
into the fitting room.
-Okay.
-[Chrishell] Have fun.
[Sabrina] All right, ladies,
we have our first look.
[Amanza] Oh!
[both gasping]
[Chrishell] Oh, my God!
[Sabrina] Go ahead
and step up on the pedestal.
[Amanza] Look at your body. Can we just--
Wow.
Your body is perfect!
-Yeah. Yeah.
-[Chrishell] Oh.
How do you feel in this dress?
I think I'm confused 'cause I had
in my mind exactly what I wanted
and now I'm like,
-"I need to keep an open mind."
-Yeah.
This dress is beautiful, but not quite
that, like, "I just love it." Right?
Like your fiancé, Romain.
Okay, maybe this is more
like an ex-boyfriend. Right?
Oh, so this is, like, a Jason dress.
-I love it, but it's not the one.
-[all laughing]
[Amanza] But, it's not the one. Next!
Back to the closet!
-[Mary] Back on the hanger! Next!
-[Nicole] On to the next.
Thank God this dress is out.
The last thing you want is for your dress
to remind you of an ex. Next.
[Sabrina] Okay, guys,
we're in our next one.
[gasping]
[Nicole] Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
Mary, that does not look
like it did on the hanger.
-Really?
-[Amanza] I have goosebumps.
[Chrishell] Is this the conservative one?
This looks so sexy.
-I love this dress.
-Yes.
[Nicole] Oh, and look at...
Are you kidding me?
-You need to see how your booty looks.
-Oh yeah, get the photo.
I want to actually clamp...
I know, booty moment.
You know what I love too?
Right under the butt, it's, like, a V...
[Chrishell] Oh, my God.
I love this one so much.
[Nicole] It's so beautiful.
-Isn't the actual one--
-[Nicole] This is the one.
How do you feel, Mary?
I feel beaut... [laughing]
[Mary] I think this could be the one
and judging by your guy's react--
Amanza's crying.
[Chrishell] Aw!
You look so beautiful. [sobbing]
[Nicole] This is the one.
I mean, it's just perfect.
Plus, you are glowing in this.
[Chrishell] Yes. Your smile is
definitely different than the other dress.
-Really?
-Yes.
[Amanza] Can you bust a move?
Let's see.
Oh, yeah!
Everything has been going wrong
with this wedding,
so finally finding something
that fits just right makes me so happy.
Okay. So what are you doing
for the bachelorette party?
[sighs] I don't know exactly.
It's up in the air.
I thought about maybe
getting a penthouse suite,
having, you know, just a girl's night fun,
but I'm like, who do we invite?
Are her and Christine, like, okay now?
-Right.
-[Amanza sighs]
I feel a little out of the loop.
Yeah. Well, the whole thing with...
Mary wanted to tell Davina
that she wasn't invited to the wedding.
And then Christine told her
before she had a chance to.
[Amanza] I thought it was poor judgment.
Like, I don't think that that's cool.
[brakes screeching]
[engine revving loudly]
♪ Did I mention
You've got our attention? ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah
You've got our attention ♪
♪ Double take, double take ♪
♪ Yeah, look away
Now look away ♪
♪ Double take, double take ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
[Heather] You want to come in?
[Heather chuckles]
[Heather] Oh, there we go. [chuckles]
[Maya] You'd better know
how to open your listing.
[Heather] Righty-tighty, lefty-loosy. Hi.
How are you?
Why are you locking it?
There's hardly a bird on the street.
[Heather] Can't take any risks.
-This is nice, I like it.
-You like it?
-Yeah.
-Yeah, you think they'll like it?
They mentioned they wanna be
in the Hills maybe,
so there is no more the Hills than that.
It is a little bit farther, but...
A little bit? It's 30 minutes
to drive up from Sunset Boulevard.
You gotta put the pedal to the metal.
This house checks a lot of boxes
that my clients need.
But Nichols Canyon it's
in the middle of nowhere. [laughing]
So it might be too far for them.
But you never know.
I always want to show my clients
and let them decide.
Thanks for driving all the way
from the OC.
Anything for you, Maya.
How is it going?
Great.
I mean, I'm super happy.
We have the house in Orange County
and we have an apartment up here,
so I've been, like, splitting my time
back and forth.
-Yeah?
-I'm, like, besties
with Taylor, uh, Tarek's daughter.
-It's her birthday, right? Coming up?
-It's her birthday, yeah.
-[Heather] Oh. They're here.
-Oh, yay. Nice.
They're so sweet. Oh, you locked the door.
-[lock rattling]
-This...
-[Heather] Can we get them in?
-Hopefully they can...
-[Maya chuckles] I got you in.
-Hello.
It's not that complicated to open a door.
Hey, guys.
-[Guy] What's up?
-[Maya chuckles]
-Hi! I'm Heather. Nice to meet you.
-Hi. Nice to meet you.
-[Heather] Thanks for coming.
-Heather, Sam and Guy.
[Maya] I know Sam because he bought land
in Abbott Kinney...
-Oh!
-...in Venice, two years ago.
-Love it.
-[Maya] He bought it as an investment,
but this house is actually for him and Guy
to start hopefully a family soon.
No pressure.
-[Guy] No pressure.
-[Heather chuckles] Maya.
[Maya] So, Sam told me he wants
a nice family-friendly house.
So I thought Nichols Canyon
could be perfect.
It's a beautiful house,
let's check it out.
[Heather] Four bedrooms, three bathrooms.
So, it's a good size.
This is the living area,
newly remodeled actually.
[Sam] I love the light.
-[Heather] Do you guys cook?
-[Maya] This is where the magic happens.
I wasn't talking about
having sex on the counter.
-Just the cooking.
-[all chuckling]
Wait, the magic happens on the counter?
Not anymore, not after having a baby,
barely any magic happens.
-Just the cooking now.
-[all laughing]
[Maya] What do you guys think?
[Sam] It's nice. It's very nice.
-We just have to talk about the commute.
-The commute.
-It can be bad.
-We're used to the center.
Have you heard of, like, online shopping?
I'm kidding. [chuckles]
[Maya] Okay, let's see the bedrooms.
This is your master, which is a good size.
-[Sam] Yeah. Wow.
-[Maya] So nice.
-[Guy] So cute.
-[Sam] This actually is a big back yard
-for the Hollywood Hills.
-[Sam] There's succulents over here.
[Guy] A lot of potential. It's beautiful.
-You can get a dog first.
-[Sam laughing]
-[Maya] Maybe a baby.
-[Guy] Yeah.
It's not my place to tell you what to get
and when,
but I feel like it's a great
starter family home.
We're back.
Hey! What do you guys think?
-I like it a lot.
-You like it?
-Yes.
-You like the vibe?
-We do.
-And the vibe is good.
The light, the floors,
the skylights, the windows...
-[Sam] It has a lot of good features.
-Yeah.
Everything is perfect,
the only minor thing is...
driving up the hill.
-Oh... yes.
-[Guy] Yes.
We're hard workers. She drove from the OC,
-I flew from Miami this morning.
-I know.
Just for you to tell me it's not for us.
-So I guess we have to buy it then.
-No pressure at all, okay?
[Heather chuckling]
♪ The pressure never got me
Got Me ♪
♪ I love it in the hot seat
Hot seat ♪
♪ I'm gonna put on a show
What ♪
♪ I'm gonna make sure you know ♪
♪ That I'm a getter
I'm a getter... ♪
[Maya] What's up
with all the mosquitos in LA by the way?
I get bitten so much.
And we're selling all these houses
where whole walls disappear.
-So that's really not good.
-[Mary and Chrishell chuckling]
I'm surprised you're getting
bit out here, Maya.
-[Chrishell] Maybe you're extra sweet.
-I know, I guess. I have nice blood.
-Hello.
-[Brett] How are you, bud?
-[Chrishell] Hey, Guy.
-Good to see you, man.
-You, too.
-[Brett] Yeah.
-You here to see, Chrishell?
-Hi!
-[Guy] Hey, what's up?
-How're you doing?
-It's hot out there, right?
-Yeah.
You wanna sit?
[Chrishell]
Do you want any water or anything?
[Guy] I'm good.
Actually, hopefully this'll be quick.
Just wanna see what's going on,
why my house is not selling.
It's been on the market with you guys,
you've had it for two months now and...
-I got nothing.
-[Chrishell] I know.
The only person that wants to sell this
more than you is me.
So, I promise you I have
your best interests at heart.
I do think it'd be a good idea
to come down a little on the price
just because when I look
at what else is on the market
and comps in the area,
price per square foot is a little lower.
I don't think square feet is lower.
I mean, you're getting views,
a great yard, a very nice house.
Price per square feet,
they're getting a deal.
The house is gorgeous. It's absolutely
stunning. You did an amazing job.
But the ball is in the buyer's court
and it just... [inhales deeply]
You know, especially at this price point,
they know they have the power,
and there's a lot of inventory.
No house ever comes
without any challenges,
but this one has definitely
had quite a few.
I've had to deal with a barking dog,
some very cranky neighbors,
and we happen to be right
underneath a huge flight path.
It's one of those things where if you're
open to maybe dropping it slightly,
I think it's the best move.
-Uh...
-Let's-- Chrishell is creating
an efficient market place.
-We've held it open every single Sunday.
-[Chrishell] Every Sunday.
There's nobody out there
that doesn't know about the house.
So, there's nothing left but price.
And I do think a lot of times when
you're putting in your search keys,
what if it's not even coming up
on someone's search because...
4.5 is their absolute max,
or something like that
if they're typing it in.
The difference between people
that are buying up to four million
to the difference of people buying
up to five, you know, in the Valley,
-our pool drops by a significant amount.
-Yeah, yeah.
[Jason] By the way, I hate to interject,
but I like the idea
of a $200,000 reduction
because, guess what, we might be having
this conversation again in a month.
We'll have just shot ourselves in the foot
and wasted a $100,000 reduction.
-We might as well go for it.
-I agree.
[Guy] I mean, it kills me
to even make a reduction.
Even a $100,000.
$200,000 is more than I want.
I can meet you guys half way
if you want, we can go 4.499.
Get under that price point, you know,
under the 4.5...
I like 4.399.
-No, I'm not ready for that.
-[both laughing]
-All right.
-Alrighty, what else are we going to do?
[Jason] I think if we can get
a price reduction,
I think that that justifies us
redoubling our marketing dollars.
Fair is fair, we'll do everything again.
We'll take the full page ad out,
we'll do new open houses,
we'll do new broker opens.
That'll resend it out to everybody,
it's now back in their inbox,
I get to call all those people
that have expressed interest
that saw it in the past.
Every single person now,
I get to call them up and be like,
"Let me show it to you again."
But we can't keep remarketing
every time we get $100,000.
We can't keep throwing money
and time at this.
That's not in my hands. I'm just relying
on you guys to move this forward,
and hopefully close it,
and get that buyer there.
[Chrishell] All right, sounds good.
-Thank you, Guy.
-[Guy] Nice seeing you again.
You too. Maybe when we see each other,
-it'll be on better terms.
-I hope so.
-I really do.
-Okay, I'll talk to you soon.
All right, bye.
Thank you.
[Jason] So, 4.499?
-[Chrishell] Yeah.
-[Jason] Okay, I mean it's better.
Between you and me, we're gonna end up
at 4.299 or 4.399 before that thing sells.
I've a feeling that's not gonna be
our last conversation with him.
-About this.
-Oh, please God.
[Jason] We should give him
another broker open with an ad.
-With the new price? Okay.
-Yeah.
[Jason] Thanks.
Those aren't fun conversations, Chrishell,
but thanks for getting through it
-and handling it well.
-[Chrishell sighs]
[Maya speaking Hebrew]
-Hey, pretty lady.
-Hey, how are you?
You look like a ray of sunshine.
-[Heather] Hi.
-Hi, guys.
-[Brett] What's up, baby? How are you?
-[Christine] You look great, Amanza.
-Thank you.
-[Maya] I need to get my nails done.
I just got mine done.
Look, they have holes in them.
-[Heather] Uh-oh.
-What?
[Heather] No, shoot.
My client Collin he's
like, super, super busy,
and I'm supposed to show him
a house on Doheny.
And the only day he can do it
is this Saturday at four
and I have Tarek's daughter's
birthday party.
-[Heather] There's...
-[straw gurgling]
If I miss her birthday,
she'll be so upset,
there's no way I can miss it.
I'd totally do it,
but I'm flying 9 a.m. to Miami.
[Christine groaning]
-Christine?
-No.
Christine...
What do you really have going on?
[Christine] I'm busy.
She's busy booking her next vacation.
-[Heather] Christine, seriously...
-I can't, I have a nail appointment.
Like, at 4 o'clock?
-[Christine] Yeah.
-[Maya chuckles]
No, my nail girl is busy.
She does Ariana Grande, too.
Jason, you wanna show
Heather's listing on Doheny?
-No, I'm good.
-[Heather] Jason!
I have Tarek's daughter's birthday,
I cannot miss.
You wouldn't know,
you have no children in your life.
-I'm not commenting.
-[Heather] You guys, like, really?
How many times have I helped you guys out?
-[Heather] Chrishell?
-I'm doing this... I'm sorry,
a client I'm showing.
[Heather] You guys, anyone else?
-[Amanza] Where is the property?
-Doheny.
[Heather] It's really important
that he sees it 'cause
I don't know if I can get him
in for another month or something.
I mean, I have the kid.
My daughter has gymnastics
until two in the Valley, but...
Could you make it by four?
-I think I can make it by four.
-I'll send you all the information.
I'll put you guys in touch.
-I don't want to move this on him.
-[straw gurgling]
[Amanza] Okay.
-It's gonna be tight.
-Are you sure?
I'll just drop her off and then go.
Okay.
Yay, everyone wins.
I would really like to make amends
with Heather,
so I'm hoping that this gesture
will give us a fresh start.
If he buys the house, I'll do something
for you. How about that?
Twenty-five percent of profit to Amanza.
-Well, let's not get carried away.
-[all laughing]
[Davina] Thank you for coming.
-Thanks for showing it.
-I know, I'm excited to show you.
♪ There's nowhere like ♪
♪ Got the green light ♪
♪ I'm ready to go ♪
♪ I got to go ♪
♪ Watch me now ♪
♪ I'm ready to go ♪
♪ Look out below... ♪
I know selling this house at this price
is really tough.
But I'm up for the challenge,
and I can't fathom the idea
of Jason telling me, "I told you so."
My friend David is an agent
for a very high-end buyer.
This is a billionaire type of client
and those don't grow on trees.
-[David] More options. Thank you.
-After you.
[David] Ooh, la la.
[Davina] Yeah, does it have a wow factor?
Pretty much. You know, we see
a lot of homes, but this is beautiful.
-[David] So the master is downstairs?
-Yes, downstairs.
Yeah, overlooking the pond, very peaceful.
[David] Very zen vibes.
-I like what he's done with the grounds.
-Yeah.
It's nine bedrooms and 12 baths.
And obviously, it has a gorgeous
guesthouse as well.
-Should be enough bathrooms, I think.
-Yeah, I think so.
-Elevator?
-Yeah, elevator.
[Davina] Yeah.
This is kind of the continuation,
so you feel like
you're in the living room,
but you're outdoors.
-[David] Very resort-like.
-Exactly, right?
[Davina] Very LA.
So, tell me about your client.
The client,
-without saying much, is a family friend.
-Yeah.
-He's in biotech.
-Uh-huh. Oh, okay.
You know, obviously a billionaire.
-Yeah.
-So...
-[David] Easily can afford it.
-I love this guy already.
[David laughing]
But do you think he's flexible
with the price or?
-Um... so...
-He's asking 75, am I right?
He's asking 75 million.
-16,000 square feet home.
-Yeah.
Prime Beverly Hills.
Who came up with the price? You or...
-The seller?
-He did, the seller did. Yeah.
So, let her have it for 75.
Okay.
-I don't wanna crush your feelings.
-So-- No, I know.
-He's just very firm on his price.
-Right.
But I think that when he sees an offer
he might be more flexible.
-How firm is he?
-I don't wanna offend him either,
but certainly I'd love to at least
generate an offer to get it going.
You know how people are when they see
an offer they might change their feelings
and their attitude.
Like, What number are you thinking?
-I mean, to be honest with you...
-Yeah.
It's beautifully done.
Beautiful house, beautiful location.
But I think we're talking mid-50s.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-You know what I mean?
If it's meant to be, it will be.
♪ I've been making millions
And I spend it on the dance floor ♪
♪ Every time I run out
I go out and I just make more ♪
♪ So put some rhythm in your feeling
Till you're moving your feet ♪
♪ Now put your hands up to the ceiling
And get down on the beat ♪
♪ But if it's wrong
And you're feeling like... ♪
♪ And you're feeling... ♪
[door beeping]
[ringing tone]
[on phone] Hi, this is Heather.
Heather, hey. It's Colin.
So, I'm at the house, but nobody is here.
[Heather] Amanza's not there yet?
Nobody's there and I have
a bit of a tight time frame today.
I gotta leave by, like, 5:30 p.m.
[Heather] Oh, my gosh.
Um... she was supposed to be there
early to meet you, so...
that's not good at all.
I can stay for, like, another 15 minutes.
[Heather] Okay, Colin.
I'm so, so, so sorry.
Let me figure out where she is
and why she's not there yet, okay?
All right. Thanks, Heather.
-Great. I'll keep you posted.
-All right.
-Okay. Bye, Collin.
-Bye.
[beeping]
[brakes screeching, car door opens]
[car door slams shut]
-Hi!
-[Colin] Hi.
I'm Amanza.
-Colin, nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you, Colin.
Sorry, I'm late. Crazy day, a little bit
last minute jumping in for Heather.
She's at her boyfriend's
daughter's birthday.
I've got two kids.
My hair, like,  literally dried out
the window on the way here.
-Make up in the car.
-I get it.
-So, I'm here.
Let's hope that this is worth the wait.
The wait will be worth... the wait.
[laughing]
-Perfect.
-The house will be worth the wait.
I didn't plan on being late.
I put in the time and I researched
the house and I'm ready to sell it.
Nice.
♪ Everybody watch now
I'mma do my thing ♪
♪ Yeah, I'mma do my thing ♪
[Amanza] Where do you live now?
I live in downtown, actually.
-So this is a really big transition.
-So...yeah.
Going from a high-rise building.
Everyone changes your light bulbs for you.
-I'll have to do it myself.
-You're rowing up.
So yeah, it's beautiful.
-It's 3,100 square feet.
-[Colin] Okay.
It's mid-century modern,
completely renovated.
-I love how it's an open flow all the way.
-Oh, yeah.
[Amanza] Beautiful Fleetwood doors
in the sunken living room.
This is a pretty chill area.
Are you a reader?
-Plenty of built in bookshelves.
-I'm not a reader.
They'll have to throw in the books
or it's gonna be bare and embarrassing.
[Amanza] Do you cook at all?
[Colin] I don't cook.
[Amanza] There's a great kitchen in case
you have somebody to cook for you.
The three bedrooms are this way.
Let's have a look at the master.
-Beautiful fireplace.
-[Colin] Nice. Another fireplace.
Then the beautiful doors open up to...
[Colin] The best part. Wow.
It's great. It's your own little oasis.
-It's so quiet, right?
-It's perfect.
The flow is so just nice. You come out
the double doors in the back
-and we're back in the living room.
-All right.
-[Amanza] What do you think?
-I think it's great.
I think that it's perfect.
Heather will be happy to hear this.
I may have been late, but I basically
landed this deal for Heather.
So, you're welcome, Heather.
-You did a good job.
-Nice.
-Better late than never.
-Do I get Heather's commission?
You guys can work that out.
[ringing tone]
Hey, Colin. It's Heather
with the Oppenheim Group.
-[Colin on phone] Hey. How are you?
-I'm good. How are you?
[Colin] I'm great. How was the party?
Um... [laughing]
She told you about the party.
Yeah, no. It was my boyfriend's
daughter's ninth birthday, so...
Wow, really, Amanza?
You told him about my personal business?
It's not cool at all.
I think she's honestly
just sometimes in her own world
and doesn't realize
that she has word vomit.
She needs to be
a little bit more professional
and be careful what she says to people.
The whole family was there and, uh...
So, it was definitely something
I could not miss.
You know, once again,
I apologize for Amanza being late.
It wasn't the best impression,
so I'm really, really sorry about that.
[Colin]
It's great Amanza was able to be there
and I think we should put in an offer.
You do? Awesome, okay.
The asking price is 4.25.
I'm thinking maybe we go in at, like,
3.85, 3.9, somewhere around there.
Yeah, I was kind of thinking
more, like, 3.7.
Three-seven? Okay, well,
I think it's an aggressive offer,
but I can submit it and tell them
that we're not gonna come in any higher.
Don't get too excited, um...
but let's be optimistic
and when I get to the office,
I'm almost there, I will submit the offer
and then I'll keep you posted.
[Colin] Sounds good,
I'll talk to you soon.
Hopefully there's no more birthdays
that come up
during the negotiation process.
Yeah.
♪ I've gone and hit the nail on the head ♪
♪ Where did this break
Call it hashtag blessed ♪
♪ I got it, I got it ♪
♪ You want it, you want it ♪
-[Brett] Look at that, man.
-Stay out of it.
Come on, bro.
♪ You keep it fly
I turn it up ♪
♪ 'Cause what you have
It ain't enough ♪
-[Mary] Hey, girl! You clean up well.
-[Amanza chuckling]
-How are you? Hi!
-How are you?
[Chrishell] Hi, beautiful.
Oh, my gosh, that's such a fun dress.
[Mary] Oh, thank you.
You know, let me try it.
[cork pops]
-[Jason] Boom.
-[Romain] Oh, my God.
Who taught you how to open
a bottle of wine? Peel that thing off.
[Romain sighs]
♪ I got it, I got it ♪
-[Heather] Hi.
-[Mary] How are you?
-Hi, Romain.
-Hi.
[Jason] Romain, Brett took the meat.
[Mary] Did you just seriously
take the entire piece of meat?
I did. I'm gonna give some to Romain,
don't worry.
Do you want some, too?
-Mwah.
-[Christine] How are you?
Good to see you!
Don't mind if I do.
[cork pops loudly]
-[Brett] Jesus Christ!
-Sorry, I had to.
[Brett] Can you warn me first
before I lose an eye?
[indistinct chattering]
[Heather] It has, like, a good vibe
for, like, a house--
[indistinct chatter]
Trust fall.
[Mary] At least
my other one made up for it.
I know, right?
-You good?
-Hi, Amanza.
Good to see you.
The beet salad is so good.
[Mary] Jason is throwing a dinner party.
This is just kind of what we do
at the Oppenheim Group.
We're all very close, we're like family.
But I'm still just kind of blown away
by the fight that Christine and I had.
I'm hoping that by keeping
my distance from her,
we can just make it through
this dinner in one piece.
[Jason] Ladies, Brett, Romain,
let's cheers.
For no reason at all
other than I love you guys.
-[all] Aw!
-Cheers.
Cheers.
-[Heather] Love you guys.
-[Amanza] We love you, too.
Oh, Heather, your client loved...
[Heather] Yeah, he loves Doheny.
-He was cool. He was really sweet.
-Yeah, Colin's amazing.
He's gonna write an offer on it, so...
-Good job.
-[Heather] I appreciate that.
But Amanza was late to the showing.
[laughing]
[Brett] How late are we talking?
I honestly don't remember.
Twenty-five, 30 minutes or so.
I mean, yeah, I apologize,
but I have a lot going on,
and I dropped, you know,
a lot that day to go help you.
I think next time then,  just don't say
you'll do it if you can't show up on time.
I didn't plan to not be on time.
[laughing]
Nobody plans on being late, I know.
[Jason] Tempered by the fact that
she was doing a favor and she's new...
the point is made and I would be
a lot tougher on her in six months.
And then, he also mentioned
you told him
that I was at a birthday party, so...
Just don't disclose
personal business, please.
Um...
I was there and it wasn't my showing,
I was doing you a favor.
I did my best.
I think this girl has enough
on her plate, too.
-She's a single mother right now.
-We're all balancing a lot.
It doesn't matter if it's, like,
a birthday party...
Like, kids-- We all have a lot going on.
Why don't you have Amanza show
all your showings,
and then you can just do what you want.
It's about being professional
for work, though.
You were at a birthday party.
Don't clap back at me that,
"I'm at a birthday party."
I asked for a favor
and you said you would do it.
[Brett] Drop the mic, Heather.
It's not worth it. It's not worth it.
[Mary] You guys have the luxury
of having nannies and everything.
Oh, Mary.
[Heather] Don't bring that into it.
If you have a nanny, you have money,
then yeah, you can do a lot.
But if you don't, things are not easy.
For her to give Amanza
so much crap about it,
I think she's in for a rude awakening.
Mary, you're defending her
because she's your best friend.
[Mary] I am.
She's also going through a lot right now.
That's also another thing.
Don't make me feel guilty
because I went to my
you know, stepchild's birthday party.
I shouldn't have gone to the party,
but, like, what am I gonna do?
-You know, it's been planned for months.
-[Brett] Mm-hmm.
Months? You've only been
dating Tarek for a few weeks.
-[Heather] So?
-[Brett] Oh, she called you out.
Months?
-We were dating for months.
-[Maya] Fine.
-[all laughing]
-[Maya] One month.
[laughing]
[Maya] So guys,
you know how, like, people,
they always joke that the girls
are moving so fast in the office?
[Jason] Are you setting yourself up
for a bad joke?
[Heather] No, don't say...
I'm pregnant.
[all] What?
-No way.
-[Maya] Very early.
[Chrishell] Oh, my God!
[Mary] Congratulations!
That's awesome.
[Amanza] Congrats.
-Were you guys trying?
-Didn't you have a baby six hours ago?
-I know!
-[Davina] Last week.
[Brett] Seriously, Maya.
Wait. Maya, this time can I say cheers?
Go for it, Chrishell.
-[Mary] Cheers.
-To the baby!
-[all] Cheers!
-[overlapping chatter]
[all laughing]
[Mary] Jason...
[indistinct chatter]
[Jason] Stop shaking!
[Christine] So, how are you
keeping it all together?
Kids, you having to work
full-fucking-time, you know?
Honestly, I breakdown, you know?
Sometimes.
You're doing your best.
Your best is more than all we're doing.
I'm late everywhere I go now.
I was... I was late.
Don't apologize for... being late.
-Oh!
-You're doing a great job.
[Amanza] Thanks.
Don't ever feel bad.
Thank you.
I don't know how you do it, Amanza.
It's my duty, I have to. You know.
So are you excited about
your bachelorette party?
-I am.
-Yeah, it's gonna be so fun, I'm sure.
But I just want some kind of smallish
and just kind of chill.
-No drama.
-Yes.
No drama. Oh, my God.
[Mary] Yeah.
You and Christine,
Did you work things out?
Is she coming?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
I haven't asked Amanza.
To really sit down and talk with you,
I haven't done this, so...
[indistinct chatter]
I'm going to bring this up now
just because we're talking openly.
[chuckling]
I was a little bit upset with you,
like, a couple of weeks ago
when the whole
Davina and Mary thing happened
because I felt like when you told Davina,
before Mary had a chance to,
and I said some things.
I didn't quite understand it
and I felt like it hurt Mary.
I understand that, I mean...
My position-- You have to understand
I was so loyal to Mary.
So much that this one doesn't
even talk to me anymore because of it.
So I defended Mary to the bone.
And she was like, "I don't care,
I didn't ask for this."
So, time went by and Mary just, like,
left me in the dust,
and you came back into the picture.
Mary wasn't there for me.
She never asked me how I got engaged.
-[Amanza] Why didn't you tell her?
-[Christine] I mean...
I didn't tell anyone.
-I feel like--
-Well, that's you guys.
That's that.
My position on this was just, like,
I would have said,
"Mary, if you don't tell Davina
by tomorrow, I'll tell her."
I didn't need to give Mary an ultimatum.
Like, I'm not a child.
I think that's an adult...
-way, not a child.
-Being an adult
is having a conversation prior
before everyone else is involved,
and she didn't do that.
[indistinct chattering]
[Amanza] Hmm...
[Christine] You know?
Hey.
[indistinct chatter]
[Amanza sighs]
[Jason] What are you girls getting into?
Bullshit.
♪ Welcome to Hollywood ♪
♪ Hollywood ♪
♪ Where the fame is only 15 seconds ♪
♪ Every face is like a glittering record ♪
♪ Hollywood ♪
♪ Like a glittering...
Welcome to Hollywood ♪